(Penny:)This is kind of creepy.
(Sheldon:)We're not supposed to
talk during this part.
(Clerk:)Sorry.
(Penny:)This is kind of creepy.
(Penny:)Do you want to stop?
(Penny:)I know you have trouble
with eye contact.
(Sheldon:)Well, you have a brown fleck
(Sheldon:)in your right iris that looks
(Sheldon:)like a Formula One race car.
(Sheldon:)So... I'm just
concentrating on that.
(Sheldon:)Plus, it's easier around people
that I'm comfortable with.
(Penny:)Aw, sweetie,
I'm comfortable around you, too.
(Sheldon:)Of course you are,
I'm warm and soothing.
(Sheldon:)I'm like a human bowl
of tomato soup.
(Penny:)I meant more like
a little brother.
(Sheldon:)Oh.
(Sheldon:)Well, I suppose I do think
of you as a sister.
(Sheldon:)And sometimes, a mother.